Let me now quickly introduce you to Bootstrap,
现在 让我快速地向你介绍你一下 Bootstrap
the front-end UI framework that we're gonna deal with in this course.
这个我们将在这门课程中主要学习的 前端界面框架
Bootstrap, as described on its own website,
正如它的网页所描述的那样 Bootstrap 是最流行的
says that it is the most popular HTML, CSS, and JavaScript based framework for
用来设计响应式和移动优先项目的
developing responsive, mobile first projects on the web.
基于 HTML CSS 和 JavaScript 的框架
This is definitely true that Bootstrap is one of the most
毋庸置疑的是 在 万维网设计方面
widely used frameworks for web design.
Bootstrap 是最广为使用的框架之一
Now, when you look at the bootstrap framework itself, it is a framework
当你学习了 Bootstrap 框架后 你会发现这个框架
designed for enabling people to design websites faster and easier.
能让你更易更快地设计网站
It provides a lot of interesting HTML, CSS, and JavaScript based templates.
它提供了大量有趣的基于 HTML CSS 和 JavaScript 的模板
Which you will encounter as we go through this course.
我们在这门课程中将学习到其中的一些
And enables us to design websites very quickly using these components.
它们将让你设计网站的速度大大加快
And Bootstrap has built-in support for
同时 Bootstrap 有着对 使用移动优先方案进行响应式设计的
responsive design using the mobile first approach.
内置的支持
We will see in the next few lessons, how the responsive
我们将会通过若干节课来讲解
mobile-first approach of Bootstrap can be leveraged to design responsive websites.
如何利用 Bootstrap 移动优先的方法 来设计响应式网站
Bootstrap was first released in 2011 by Mark Otto and Jacob Thornton.
Bootstrap 是由 Mark Otto 和 Jacob Thornton 在 2011 年首次发布的
They were Twitter employees that designed Bootstrap for
它们都是 Twitter 的雇员 且 Bootstrap 一开始的目的
their own use within the company.
是给他们公司内部使用
And then, later, decided to make it open source.
然后过了一段时间后 他们决定开源
Currently Bootstrap is in version 3.3.5.
现在最新的 Bootstrap 版本是 3.3.5
4.0 is already on the horizon, will be released soon.
而 4.0 版本也将很快发布
Bootstrap has maintained backward compatibility as far as possible,
Bootstrap 对于向后兼容的维护做得非常充分
but Bootstrap 3 was a big step forward in supporting
不过 Bootstrap 3 在对 响应式 web 设计的支持上
responsive web design in a much better manner than earlier versions of Bootstrap.
比起先前的 Bootstrap 而言 有一个大飞跃
So, definitely it is worth considering and
综上所述 学习 Bootstrap 是非常值得的
worth learning because it was one of the first comprehensive frameworks
因为它是第一个我们能用的
that was available for use.
综合性的框架
So we'll move on to the next lesson,
那么接下来我们将进行下一节课的学习
where we will first get familiar with Bootstrap and how to make use of Bootstrap
在那里 我们将会了解到 Bootstrap 的更多细节 以及如何
within our project.
在我们的项目中应用 Bootstrap 翻译: Carefree0910 | 审阅: Saul Qunming Yuan Coursera Global Translator Community